const cards = [
    { 
        question: "Time complexity of searching in a balanced BST?", 
        answer: "O(log n)" 
    },
    { 
        question: "Difference between stack and queue?", 
        answer: "Stack LIFO Queue FIFO" 
    },
    { 
        question: "How does a hash table handle collisions?", 
        answer: "Linked list for collisions" 
    },
    { 
        question: "Worst-case time complexity of quicksort?", 
        answer: "O(n^2)" 
    },
    { 
        question: "Worst-case time complexity of mergesort?", 
        answer: "O(n log n)" 
    },
    { 
        question: "What is a heap and its types?", 
        answer: "Binary tree with heap property" 
    },
    { 
        question: "Graph traversal using a queue?", 
        answer: "BFS" 
    },
    { 
        question: "Difference between DFS and BFS?", 
        answer: "Deep first vs. Broad first" 
    },
    { 
        question: "Purpose of Dijkstra's algorithm?", 
        answer: "Shortest path in a graph" 
    },
    { 
        question: "Data structure for a priority queue?", 
        answer: "Binary heap" 
    }
];

export { cards };